## **RABIA UMAIR**

## Computer Engineer

+92 344 2981144

Rabiaumair334@gmail.com

Karachi, Pakistan

# EDUCATION

#### Bachelor of Computer Science 2014-2018

**Bahria University** 

Pre-Engineering 2012-2014

Defence Authority Collage For Women (D.C.W)

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Management Skills
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Communication Skills
- Problem Solving
- Conceptual and IT skills
- Client Relationships
- Document Control
- Report production

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Urdu

#### **PROFILE**

An innovative thinker, initiative taker and multi dimensional professional with exceptional logical and analytical skills possesses experience as a computer science engineer. Strong motivational and leadership skills and ability to work under pressure and time span individually or in team. A little know how of programming languages and database.

#### **SKILLS**

- Data Analysis / Visualization & data handling
- Microsoft Office
- Leadership & Collaboration
- Logo Designing
- Data Entry
- Email Managements
- Spreadsheets

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Universal logistics and Cargo**

Administrative assistant

2018-2020

- Drafted 10+ emails daily for HR staff in regards to company policies, events, and trainings.
- Communicated with staff to schedule meetings and assist them as needed.
- Managed content, and SEO Marketing, Branding and Logo Design
- Handled calendar management and filing systems accurately.

## **Pak Petro Company**

Administrative Coordinator

2021-2023

- Working with the wider development team.
- Managed 6+ administrative staff, empowering them to perform their tasks effectively.
- Composed written documentation and maintained department databases.
- Planned and coordinated events to ensure staffing and locations were accurately accommodated.
- Supported senior management with company scheduling and meetings.
- Provided exceptional customer service when handling in-person, phone, or email interactions with clients.